{
    "id": "8d87250dfa6e4dfcae47204ec11290e8",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am looking …………………… my keys.",
            "description": "To look for something is to search for it. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t agree …………………….. you.",
            "description": "We agree with a person, opinion or policy.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot count …………………… him.",
            "description": "To count on somebody is to trust them.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He belongs …………………… a warrior clan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They took him to hospital after he complained …………………… uneasiness.",
            "description": "You complain of a problem.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "about",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is still dependent ………………………. his parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the eldest ……………………… the four siblings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was amazed ……………………… her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good ……………………. solving puzzles.",
            "description": "We say good at, bad at, poor at etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience were enthralled ………………………. the spectacular performance of the children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ………………………. me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn't seem perturbed ............................... the commotion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}